<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Dana J. Ardell | Work on Dana J. Ardell | UX Designer</title><link>https://www.danajardell.com/portfolio/</link><description>Recent content in Dana J. Ardell | Work on Dana J. Ardell | UX Designer</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 16:48:28 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.danajardell.com/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Designing a User-Friendly Online Cannabis Marketplace</title><link>https://www.danajardell.com/portfolio/leafly-usability/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 07:31:26 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://www.danajardell.com/portfolio/leafly-usability/</guid><description>Project Overview Our team conducted a series of usability evaluations of Leafly.com, including a heuristic evaluation, a cognitive walkthrough, a usability test, and a comparative usability test.</description></item><item><title>Improving Accessibility to Fashion for People Who &lt;nobr>Are Blind&lt;/nobr></title><link>https://www.danajardell.com/portfolio/blind-fashion/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 19:34:38 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://www.danajardell.com/portfolio/blind-fashion/</guid><description>Design Brief Project Overview Type of Project: Pre-Design This type of project is exploratory and focuses on understanding the needs of a user group to inform the design of a new assistive technology (AT) or application.</description></item><item><title>Redesigning a Major Modern Art Museum's Website</title><link>https://www.danajardell.com/portfolio/mca-ia/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 23:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.danajardell.com/portfolio/mca-ia/</guid><description>Design Brief Project Overview Type of Project: Information Architecture The Museum of Contemporary Art website (MCA) is a museum website where users can book tickets, browse exhibitions, and search museum programs about contemporary art in Chicago.</description></item><item><title>Simplifying Plant Care for New and &lt;nobr>Experienced Users&lt;/nobr></title><link>https://www.danajardell.com/portfolio/simplifying-plant-care/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Mar 2022 23:06:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.danajardell.com/portfolio/simplifying-plant-care/</guid><description>Design Brief Project Overview Type of Project: Iterative Design and Prototyping With the Evergreen app and smart pot system, plant owners can manage multiple plants, monitor real-time metrics for optimal plant health, schedule care reminders, and receive personalized recommendations vetted by experts.</description></item></channel></rss>